A Guide to the Governor Robert F. McDonnell, Policy Office, Records, 1997; 2007-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
Library of Virginia
- IV. Subject Files, 1997; 2007-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)., Extent: 18.5 cubic feet (53 boxes). (Box 57-109)
  - Subseries IV.C. Melissa Laughner, Deputy Director of Policy, 2008-2011., Extent: 0.7 cubic feet (2 boxes) (Box 76-77)
    - INOVA - Fairfax Hospital, 2009-2010. (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Prevent Blindness Mid-Atlantic (PBMA): Save Our Sight (SOS), 2010. (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - State Employees, 2008. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Health Exchange, 2010. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Medicaid Audit, 2010. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Solutions to Affordable Health Insurance for Working Virginia Families and Individuals, 2009. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Southeastern Virginia Training Center (SEVTC), 2010. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Lake Taylor Transitional Care Hospital, undated. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Children's Hospital of the King's Daughters (CHKD), 2010. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Community Options, Inc., 2010. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Medical Malpractice Settlement, undated. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Health and Human Resources Work Group, 2010. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Retail Clinics, 2011. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Health Care Association (VHCA), Medicaid, 2010. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Med Solutions, Medicaid, 2010. (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - MAXIMUS, State Health Plans, 2010. (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - HIS Global Insight, 2010. (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Voices of Virginia's Children, 2010. (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - GEO Care, Sexual Violent Predator, undated. (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Center for Behavioral Rehabilitation (VCBR), 2011. (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Draft Pre-File Legislation, 2009. (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Subseries IV.D. Julia Ciarlo Hammond, Director of Legislative Affairs and Policy Advisor, 2010-2014., Extent: 2.68 cubic feet (8 boxes) (Box 78-85)
    This subseries is housed in eight (8) boxes. The original order has been maintained. On 3 January 2011, Governor Robert F. McDonnell announced the appointment of Julia Ciarlo Hammond as Director of Legislative Affairs. Hammond lead the administration's legislative strategy, helped develop Governor McDonnell's policy agenda and secured its support in the General Assembly. She provided guidance and direction to the Cabinet and their staff on legislative issues in state agencies and oversaw all interaction with the General Assembly. She worked with the governor's policy team to elevate, cultivate and strengthen the administration's key relationships with lawmakers, allies, and stakeholders. Hammond was responsible for the management of policy and messaging with the Secretariats of Agriculture and Forestry, Commerce and Trade, Education, Health and Human Resources, and Transportation. Hammond served until the end of the McDonnell administration in January 2014.
    Notable subjects in this subseries include: Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, Governor's Commission on Government Reform, Efficiency and Restructuring, education reform, Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Privatization, and transportation reform.
    - Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, Small Business, 2010. (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, Small Business, 2010. (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Locality Resolutions Opposing Budget Cuts, 6 September 2011. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Tax Reform, September-October 2011. (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Government Reform Private Work Groups (1 of 2), 19 October 2011. (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Government Reform Private Work Groups (2 of 2), 19 October 2011. (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Government Reform Work Groups (1 of 2), November 2011. (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Government Reform Work Groups (2 of 2), November 2011. (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - K-12 Education Reform, November 2011. (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Budget Amendments, Talking Points for HB 1300 and HB 1301, May 2012. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Secretary of Education, Strategic Plan Update, July 2012. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Policy Venture to New Orleans, Louisiana, 8-10 October 2012. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates Meeting, 19 November 2012. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Virginia's Road to the Future, Governor McDonnell's 2013 Legislative Package for Transportation Funding and Reform, January 2013. (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - All Students: The Opportunity to Learn, K-12 Policy Retreat, University of Virginia (1 of 2), April 2013. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - All Students: The Opportunity to Learn, K-12 Policy Retreat, University of Virginia (2 of 2), April 2013. (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - National Governors Association (NGS), Medicaid Health Care Purchasing Compendium, September 2013. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Work Groups: Education
      - Time is the Enemy, Complete College America, September 2011. (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - JLARC: Coordination Needs within Virginia's Education System, 2011. (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Post-Labor Day School Opening, 2011. (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Qualified School Construction Bonds (QSCB), 2010-2011. (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Education Policy, 2011-2012. (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Education - Massie Bill (HB 2314), 2011. (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Race to the Top, 2011. (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Education-General, 2011. (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Education-Virtual Schools, 2011. (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Education-Charter Schools, 2011. (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - ALL STUDENTS, 2012. (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Education Tax Credits, 2012. (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - K-12 Education Legislation, 2011. (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Privatization, 2010. (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Privatization, 2010. (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Privatization, 2011 Session, 2010-2011. (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Towing and Recovery Operators, 2011. (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Government Reform Commission, 2011. (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Submission of Agency Legislative Proposals for the 2012 Session, 2011. (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - House, Education Reform, A-F Speeches, undated. (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - 2011 Re-enrolled Bills, 2011. (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Bill Signings, 2011. (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Transportation Meeting, 2011. (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Budget Amendments, 2012. (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Commerce and Trade Amendments, 2012. (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Health and Human Resources Amendments, 2012. (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Other Amendments, 2012. (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Transportation Amendments, 2012. (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Retirement System (VRS) Reform Legislation, 2012. (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Transportation Legislation, 2012. (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Government Reform Commission Board Recommendations, 2011. (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program (SNAP), undated. (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Business, Professional and Occupation License (BPOL) Study Information, 2010. (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - North-South Corridor Project, 2013. (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - 2013 Budget, 2012. (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - The Governor's K-12 Education Reform Summit, 15-16 August 2012. (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Education Amendments, 2012. (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Governor's Holiday Hoops Classic, 2011-2012. (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - 2011 Legislative Session Prep, 2011. (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Education Reform, A-F, 2013. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Health Benefit Exchange, 2011. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - 2011 Legislative Package. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Messaging - Post 2012 Legislative Session. (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Embryonic Stem Cell Research, 2012. (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Meeting Notes, 2011-2012. (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Commonwealth of Opportunity 2012 Statewide Tour, 2012. (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Transportation Reform Financing, 2012. (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Public Safety Bill Signing, 3 July 2013. (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - 2012-2013 Legislative Contacts, 2012. (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Budget Development, 2011. (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Budget Related Documents, 2012. (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Health Reform Initiative Advisory Council Meeting, 15 July 2011. (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Health Reform Initiative Advisory Council Meeting, 9 September 2011. (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Health and Human Resources Initiative Briefing, 7 September 2011. (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - 2013 Agency Legislative Ideas, undated. (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Health Benefit Exchange Expansion, 2012. (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Regulation Reform Bills, 2013. (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Privatization, The PMF Group, 2010-2011. (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Privatization, 2010. (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Government Reform
      - Taxes, 2011. (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - North Carolina Regulatory Reform, 2011. (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - Board Elimination, 2011. (Box 85, Folder 10)
      - Ideas and Legislation, 2011. (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - Office of the State Inspector General, 2011. (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation
      - Small Business Subgroup, 2010. (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - Final Jobs Commission Meeting, 30 September 2010. (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Loose Documents, 2010-2011; 2013-2014; undated. (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Subseries IV.E. Generra Peck, Special Assistant for Policy Development; Deputy Director of Legislative Affairs and Policy Development, 2010-2013., Extent: 2.63 cubic feet (8 boxes) (Box 86-93)
    This subseries is housed in eight (8) boxes and is grouped into two categories: Briefing/Subject Binders and Subject Files. The original order has been maintained. Peck served the McDonnell administration in a variety of positions. From January 2010 to June 2011, she served as Special Assistant for Commerce and Trade. She served as staff on the Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation assigned to the Business Development and Recruitment and Energy Work Groups. In June 2011, Peck was appointed Special Assistant for Policy Development. She was responsible for research, policy analysis and legislative development related to policy development and the Commission on Government Reform, Efficiency and Restructuring. In September 2013, Peck was promoted to Assistant Director of Legislative Affairs and Strategic Initiatives. Peck aided in the development of legislative strategy and the Governor's policy agenda. Peck conducted policy analysis related to education, entrepreneurship, technology, innovation and government reform. She served until the end of the McDonnell administration in January 2014.
    Notable subjects in this subseries include: Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, Governor's Commission on Government Reform, Efficiency and Restructuring, and education reform.
    - Briefing/Subject Binders
      - Operational Review Task Force, 2010. (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Government Reform and Restructuring Commission, Work Group Materials, 2011. (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Local Mandates Review, Stakeholder and Agency Comments (1 of 3), undated. (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Local Mandates Review, Stakeholder and Agency Comments (2 of 3), undated. (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Local Mandates Review, Stakeholder and Agency Comments (3 of 3), undated. (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - 2012 General Assembly Session, 2012. (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - 2012 General Assembly Reconvened Session, Governor's Amendment and Veto Key Points, 2012. (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - 2013 General Assembly Session, 2013. (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - 2013 General Assembly Session, K-12 Education Legislation and Budget Proposals, 2012. (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Virginia's Road to the Future, Governor McDonnell's 2013 Legislative Package for Transportation Funding and Reform, 2013. (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Common Core State Standards and the Virginia Standards of Learning, July 2012. (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - The Governor's K-12 Education Reform Summit, 15-16 August 2012. (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Education Strategic Initiatives, 2012. (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - ALL STUDENTS Policy Discussion, November-December 2012. (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - Energy Policy Subject Briefing, 2012. (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Small Business Subject Briefing, 2011. (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Workforce Development Subject Briefing, 2011. (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Research and Technology Strategic Initiatives, 2011-2012. (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Governor's Holiday Hoops Classic, December 2012 and December 2013, 2010-2013. (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Rural Jobs Council, 2013. (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - e-Region Economic Development Tour, Fall 2011. (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - The Year of the Entrepreneur, 2012. (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Policy Venture to Research Triangle Park, 20 June 2012. (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - National Governors Association (NGA) Annual Meeting, Planning Group, July 2012. (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Virginia's Race to the Top Competitive Application, Briefing for Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 22 April 2010. (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Virginia Schools Denied Accreditation-Alexandria, Norfolk, Petersburg, November 2013. (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files
      - Texas Compact, 2011. (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Waiting for Superman, June 2012. (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Scholarship Tax Credit-Guidelines and 2013 Bill, 2012. (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Social Entrepreneurship in Virginia, 2012. (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Sharepoint, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Sparked.com Small Business, undated. (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - StartUp America Partnership and Entrepreneur Eco System, 2012. (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Governor's Commonwealth of Opportunity Statewide Tour, 7-12 May 2012. (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Strategic Planning McDonnell Administration Priorities, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Surplus Trigger Research, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Red Carpet Tour, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Review of Governor Email Accounts, 7 July 2011. (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Regulatory Review, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - PE Bill (SB 471), 2012. (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - McDonnell Leadership Luncheon, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - North Carolina Regulatory Reform Ideas, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - Interior Designers, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 14)
      - 2011 Governor's Fellows. (Box 91, Folder 15)
      - Intellectual Property/Piracy Issues, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 16)
      - Labor Day School Opening, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 17)
      - Henricus, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 18)
      - Commerce and Trade Housing Policy, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 19)
      - Governor's Small Business Summit Conference Planning Group, 2011. (Box 91, Folder 20)
      - Hampton Roads Legislative Roundtable, 15 September 2011. (Box 91, Folder 21)
      - Governor's 2011 Holiday Hoops Classic Announcement, 10 August 2011. (Box 91, Folder 22)
      - Golden Dogwood Senior Discount Card, undated. (Box 91, Folder 23)
      - 2011 Governor's Fellows Projects. (Box 91, Folder 24)
      - Federal Mandates Research, 2011-2012. (Box 91, Folder 25)
      - Electronic Meetings, HB 1105 (Greason), 2012. (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Department of Economic Development, Ideas and Research, 2011. (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Governor's Easter Egg Hunt, 2012. (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Commerce and Trade Work Group, 2011. (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - CMS Research - Competitive Bidding, 2011. (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Constant Contact Account, 2011. (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Cherbo Project, 2012. (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Business Plan Competition, 2011. (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Biotechnology Research Park, 2011. (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Budget Transparency, 2011. (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Agency Head Summit, Fall 2011. (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Virginia Code Approval, 31 December 2013. (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Virginia Code Approval, 18 December 2013. (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Subseries IV.F. Christy Morton, Deputy Director of External Affairs and Policy Development, 2009-2013., Extent: 2.80 cubic feet (8 boxes) (Box 94-101)
    This subseries is housed in eight (8) boxes. The original order has been maintained. In June 2011, Governor Robert F. McDonnell announced the appointment of Christy Tomlinson Morton as Deputy Director of External Affairs and Policy Development. Morton served as a liaison to outside constituencies to facilitate communications with the administration. She worked with stakeholders and outside organizations to communicate their priorities to the administration as well as to inform their constituencies and organizations about Governor McDonnell's policy initiatives. She also participated in the Governor's Commission on Government Reform, Efficiency and Restructuring. Morton left the administration on 19 August 2013.
    - Outreach
      - Abortion, 2011-2012. (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Agriculture, 2011. (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Americans for Tax Reform (ATR), 2011. (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Bill Signing Ceremonies, 2011. (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Bio Tech, undated. (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - BLAST Mentoring, 2011. (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Board of Towing and Recovery Operators (BTRO), 2011. (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Budget Outreach, December 2011. (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - 2012 Budget Stakeholder Outreach, 2012. (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - 2012 Budget, 2011-2012. (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - 2012 Budget Outreach, 2011-2012. (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Campaign Policy Proposals, 2011. (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Center Right, 2011. (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Community Relations, 2011. (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - CRM, undated. (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - Virginia Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation (DPOR), 2012. (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - Education, 2011-2012. (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Faith-Based Outreach, 2011. (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Family Foundation, 2012. (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - General Assembly Members, 2011. (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Government Reform, 2011-2012. (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Health and Human Resources (HHR), 2011-2012. (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Hurricane, 2011. (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Human Trafficking, 2011. (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 2011. (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Line of Duty Act (LODA), 2011. (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Local Legislative Agendas, 2011-2012. (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Mandate Review, 2011-2012. (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Mercatus Center, 2011. (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Military/Veterans, 2011. (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Minority Outreach, 2011-2012. (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Outreach Plan, 2011-2012. (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Policy Development, 2011. (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Policy Office, 2011-2012. (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - 2012 Post Session Outreach (1 of 2), 2012. (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - 2012 Post Session Outreach (2 of 2), 2012. (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - 2013 Post Session Outreach, 2012-2013. (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Public Safety, 2012. (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Red Carpet Tour, 2011. (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Regional Business Symposium, Blacksburg, 9 September 2011. (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Government Reform and Reorganization (1 of 2), 2011. (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Government Reform and Reorganization (2 of 2), 2011. (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - School Choice, undated. (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Small Business, 2011. (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Speeches, 2011. (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Sprint Nextel, 2011. (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Statewide Tour, 9-16 August 2013. (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Tax Reform, undated. (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Tea Party, 2011-2012. (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Think Tanks, 2011. (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Tobacco, undated. (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Tort Reform, 2011. (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Towing, 2011-2012. (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Transportation, 2011-2012. (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Valley Tour, September 2011. (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Citizens Defense League (VCDL), School Gun Safety Guidelines, 2011. (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Veterans, 2011. (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - VIP Letters, 2011-2012. (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Virginia Chamber, 2012. (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - Virginia Association of Counties (VACo), 2012. (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - Virginia Manufacturers Association (VMA), 2011-2012. (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Retirement System (VRS), 2011-2012. (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Year of the Entrepreneur (YOE), 2012. (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous, 2011-2012. (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - 2012 General Assembly Session
      - Government Reform Work Group Materials, November 2011. (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Local Mandates Review, Stakeholder and Agency Comments (1 of 3), 2012. (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Local Mandates Review, Stakeholder and Agency Comments (2 of 3), 2012. (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Local Mandates Review, Stakeholder and Agency Comments (3 of 3), 2012. (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Natural Resources
      - An Introduction to Department of Game and Inland Fisheries (DGIF), December 2009. (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, Transition Briefing, 7 December 2009. (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Office of the Governor-Elect, Report of the Policy Transition Committee on Natural Resources (1 of 3), 4 January 2010. (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Office of the Governor-Elect, Report of the Policy Transition Committee on Natural Resources (2 of 3), 4 January 2010. (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Office of the Governor-Elect, Report of the Policy Transition Committee on Natural Resources (3 of 3), 4 January 2010. (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Energy, 2011-2013. (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Energy, 2011. (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - The Virginia Energy Plan, Issued by the Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1 July 2010. (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Government Reform, 2011. (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Natural Resources, Governor and Agency Bills, 2010. (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Sunday Hunting, 2011. (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Subseries IV.G. Chad Cole, Scheduling Assistant, Deputy Travel Aide and Policy Assistant, 2010-2013., Extent: 0.88 cubic feet (3 boxes) (Box 102-104)
    This subseries is housed in three (3) boxes. The original order has been maintained. Chad Cole began serving the McDonnell administration in the summer of 2011 as a Governor's Fellow. He later was appointed Executive Research Assistant for Policy and Public Safety. In this role, Cole provided support to both offices by conducting legislative research and managing special projects as needed. On 30 November 2012, Governor Robert F. McDonnell appointed Cole as Scheduling Assistant and Deputy Travel Aide/Policy Assistant, a joint role providing support to the Governor's Scheduling and Policy Office. He helped to manage the Governor's daily commitments and also oversaw several projects pertaining to the Governor's legislative agenda. Cole left the McDonnell administration in September 2013. Records in this subseries reflect Cole's various roles within the administration.
    - Declined Invitations, April-June 2013. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Declined Invitations, December 2012-March 2013. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Log, Spring 2013. (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Add to Log, 2013. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Policy Decisions, 2011-2012. (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Highlights of Governor McDonnell's Legislative Accomplishments, 2010-2013. (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Government Reform, 2011. (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Virginia for Business, 2011. (Box 103, Folder 1)